registrydefender.com 2016-01-25

# Registry Defender: Privacy Policy

This privacy policy ("Policy") discloses the data collection and use practices of Grab Media Holdings, LLC, for its software Registry Defender ("Registry Defender") in connection with the Registry Defender Web site (the "Web Site") and all associated Registry Defender products and services (the "Registry Defender Services").

Registry Defender will not directly inform you of any changes to the privacy policy which involve use of your personal information. If at anytime you are dissatisfied with our service to you or are in disagreement with our terms and conditions or privacy policy, you reserve the option to Opt-out of our website and future communication.

## What Information We Collect/How We Use It.

We store and use the information you give us in accordance with the terms of this Policy. Our registration form (or registration information you provide our marketing partners if you joined Registry Defender though one of our partners) requests that you provide certain contact and profile information. That information includes but may not be limited to: name, address, email address, phone number, gender and birth date.

In addition, we might receive information about you from outside sources and add it to your Registry Defender membership information. We do this to improve personalization of our services (for example, providing better newsletter content, advertising or special offers that we think will interest you).

We also may collect information such as the identification of the server your computer is logged onto and whether you opened a Registry Defender e-mail delivered to you. We also may compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending identical messages to our members. You can add and modify the information you have provided by sending an e-mail to info@registrydefender.com with your requested changes.

When you submit personal information, it is kept in a secure database to ensure that is not subject to any unauthorized data usage.

We use all this information in five ways:

  * to provide you with personalized information via electronic delivery, telemarketing and/or direct mail. These may include personalized offers from 3rd party sources.
  * to send you targeted advertising via electronic delivery and/or direct mail;
  * to contact you for feedback and surveys via electronic delivery and/or direct mail;
  * to send you general and administrative information about Registry Defender via electronic delivery and/or direct mail; and
  * to provide your contact information to Registry Defender marketing partners whose offer(s) you have selected to receive in order for them to send you special offers via electronic delivery, telemarketing and direct mail.

## Use of Personal Information 

We may share non-personal, summary information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties. However, any individual customer's information provided for partners or third parties under contract with Grab Media Holdings, LLC, shall be used only to perform or complete a necessary transaction or function related to the customer's purchase. These transactions or functions shall be in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. In some cases, Grab Media Holdings, LLC, may use a visitor's personal information to understand overall patterns for web site usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue.

## Agents

We employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf.. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from customer lists, analyzing data, and providing marketing analysis. These agents have access to member personal information as needed to perform their functions for Registry Defender.

## Third-party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like to be removed from any 3rd party advertising and solicitation through E-mail, telemarketing, or direct mail please send your request to info@registrydefender.com or simply go to http://www.registrydefender.com/email.aspx and enter the email address you would like removed.

## Cookies

We use cookies to, among other things, save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Registry Defender Web Site and to deliver personalized content. Many Web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You may change your browser settings to either reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is about to be placed on your computer. Please note, however, that rejecting cookies while visiting the Registry Defender Web Site may result in certain parts of the Registry Defender Web Site not operating correctly or as efficiently as if they were allowed. For example, if you are a Registry Defender member, you may need to enter your username and password each time you visit the Registry Defender Web Site. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

## E-Mail Links

In some instances we may include certain links in our e-mails that will allow us to monitor whether you access specific content or advertisements contained in that e-mail. When you click on one of these links, we will record that click and certain activities on the Web page associated with that link. We may use this information for various purposes, such as to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior in and to our e-mail advertisements and content, and to better understand and serve you.

## Disclosures

Registry Defender may disclose information about you and your use of the Registry Defender Web Site and the Registry Defender Services if Registry Defender believes such disclosure is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law or legal process; (ii) to protect or defend the rights or property of Registry Defender or others; (iii) to enforce the Registry Defender Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy; and (iv) to respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another. In addition Registry Defender may share or transfer information about you and that you provide to Registry Defender, to one or more third party entities pursuant to a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion, or all of, the assets or stock of Registry Defender or its affiliated entities, or as otherwise provided herein.

## Reports

We periodically prepare analyses and reports reflecting visitor and member use of the Registry Defender Web Site and Registry Defender Service for our internal use as well as for a limited number of our business partners. These reports include aggregate (non-personal) information about Registry Defender members, and in certain instances, visitors to the Registry Defender Web Site. The information in these reports will not identify you individually. Our business partners who have access to these reports will not be able to contact you from the information contained in the reports.

## Links

The Registry Defender Web Site, as well as the electronic messages sent as part of the Registry Defender Service, may contain links to other sites or services. Registry Defender is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party sites. If you have a question about the privacy policy of those other sites, please contact them directly.

## Removal

To have all of your personally identifiable information removed from our database, send an e-mail request to remove@registrydefender.com and we will be happy to delete such information after we receive a request to that effect. Please be advised that by requesting that your data be removed from our database, you will be unsubscribed from the Registry Defender Service.

## Updates

Registry Defender may revise this Policy from time to time and at any time in the future to (i) improve or modify the Registry Defender Service, (ii) reflect future developments in Registry Defender data information gathering, storing and release practices, (iii) comply with applicable laws, and (iv) reflect changes in Registry Defender business structure. Depending on the nature of the change, we will notify users by e-mail (to the current e-mail address on file) and/or placing a notice on the Registry Defender Web Site.

If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, we ask that you do not register with Registry Defender, or with any of our promotional partners.

## Contact Us

Registry Defender is presented by Angle Interactive (AI).

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Registry Defender  
802 6th Avenue  
Suite 14  
New York, NY 10001  
info@registrydefender.com

USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE PRIVACY POLICY  
Effective Date January 1, 2006
